squirtingorgasmmastery.com 2014-12-03

# Squirting Mastery Privacy Policy

Overview

Squirting Mastery is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of our members. We want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for consumers, and in particular, ensure that children (i.e. anyone who is under the age of 18) are protected from adult materials. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor to Squirting Mastery, what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit www.squirtingmastery.com, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct the information.

Information about You

Upon registration for membership, Squirting Mastery will specifically ask for information about you. We will ask for your full name, billing address, telephone number and credit card number in order to ship you your products and provide you with all of Squirting Mastery's services.

We use your telephone number only if there is an order-related issue, though because we understand your need for anonymity we will make all attempts to contact you via email. We do not use your telephone number for marketing purposes.

We may also use that information to let you know of additional products and services about which you might be interested. You can choose not to receive such information if you don't want to by letting us know on the registration screen when you sign up for our service. We may ask you for information about your interests so that both you and we can take advantage of the interactivity of the online medium, but you may always choose to not respond.

Tracking Information:

Squirting Mastery will collect and store only the following nonpersonally-identifying information from you: the name of the domain name from which you access the Internet; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the Website from which you linked directly to our site. We also track your order and billing history so you can access your Squirting Mastery and immediately determine which program you've purchased and how you paid for them. This information is password-protected. No one has access to it but you.

As you browse the Squirting Mastery website, cookies are placed on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow us to track the items you select as you shop, and help us match your address and credit card information with your order so you don't need to retype the information each time you visit our site. Cookies also allow us to gather information to provide you with the best service. It tells us the number and frequency of visitors to our site and its various pages. Third parties may serve some of these cookies. We analyze this data to determine which parts of our site customers like and which parts need improvement. Automatically logged information is also used to analyze trends and to administer the site.

The only party that we may share your transaction processing information is VeriSign, which subsequently may share that information to a third party licensor of the fraud prevention scoring services (the "Fraud Service Bureau") solely for use in developing its fraud prevention modeling and for performing the Fraud Services. All your transaction processing information provided to the Fraud Service Bureau shall be subject to written agreement between VeriSign and the Fraud Service Bureau restricting disclosure of any Customer Data to other third parties except as necessary to perform the Fraud Services. Otherwise, all of your personal information such as name, address, email address and telephone number will not be shared with any third parties.

Disclosure

We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to Squirting Mastery or your personal information as described above, to any third parties. We may however share with our partners aggregated statistical information about the use of Squirting Mastery. Any exceptions to this policy of sharing your name, address or email address with a partner company will be done only with your permission.

Security and Access

Squirting Mastery uses a secure socket layer (SSL), which encrypts all information that is transmitted or received. This encryption process ensures that the information you give us is protected against unauthorized access.

We have implemented technology and security features, as well as strict internal guidelines, to safeguard the privacy of your personal information from unauthorized access or improper use. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. While we make every effort to ensure that your information is secure on our system, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

Privacy Policy Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy for Squirting Mastery, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone.

Contact

If you have any questions concerning our privacy policy you can contact us at support@2girlsteachsex.com   
  
We take your privacy very seriously. ©2001-2013 ISN Education, LLC. All Rights Reserved. This website is for ADULTS ONLY. The videos and images in this site are intended to be used by responsible adults as sexual aids, to provide sexual education and to provide sexual entertainment. If you've read and fully understand the above agreement, and you affirm and swear that viewing/downloading/receiving sexually explicit materials does not violate the standards of your community, that you won't make any of the materials available to minors in any form, that you believe it is your constitutional right to view these materials, that you are wholly liable for any legal ramifications that may arise for your receiving or viewing of these materials and that you are over the age of 18. If you do not agree exit immediately.
